<resources>
    <string name="app_name">smeme</string>
    <string name="no_diary">작성한 일기가 없어요.</string>
    <string name="menu_myDiary">내 일기</string>
    <string name="menu_explore">둘러보기</string>
    <string name="menu_collection">보관함</string>
    <string name="odir_dummy_context">The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person but sometimes some violence is needed. I was just the part of the process not The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person. needed... The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person but sometimes some violence is needed. I was just the part of the process not The issue that requires the phone call we have to The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person but sometimes some violence is needed. I was just the part of the process not The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person. needed The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person but sometimes some violence is needed. I was just the part of the process not The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person. needed The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person but sometimes some violence is needed. I was just the part of the process not The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person. needed The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person but sometimes some violence is needed. I was just the part of the process not The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person. needed The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person but sometimes some violence is needed. I was just the part of the process not The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person. neededThe issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person but sometimes some violence is needed. I was just the part of the process not The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person. needed The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person but sometimes some violence is needed. I was just the part of the process not The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person. needed The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person but sometimes some violence is needed. I was just the part of the process not The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person. neededThe issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person but sometimes some violence is needed. I was just the part of the process not The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person. needed The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person but sometimes some violence is needed. I was just need but sometimes some violence is needed. I was just the part of the process not........ solve it in person but sometimes some violence is needed... I was just the part of the process not The issue that requires the phone call we have to solve it in person but sometimes some violence is needed</string>
</resources>